our wedding cost about
$70 including cleanup fees um because we
saved all our money for what we thought
would be a good idea so um let me let me
um pass this on to you it's not a good
idea um we went on a 3-w week
honeymoon yeah 3 weeks together like
that's 21 days together like I love you
but not all in a
row
ah thanks guys I just you just you just
got to you know you got to be good at
giving compliments that's one thing like
um some people say when you get married
you give up not me I if we're going out
somewhere I like to curl my bangs up
real
tight I make a tight curl and I'm in the
bathroom room about half an hour and
smoke is coming out of the
iron but I'm trying and then I go out to
the living room and present myself like
a
gift yeah yeah and he looks at me he's
like oh it looks like you got an awning
on your
forehead oh thank you I
think